(Leonard:)Hey.
(Sheldon:)What are you trying to pull?
(Sheldon:)The president of
science isn't in here.
(Leonard:)You lie down, he'll be here
in a minute.
(Leonard:)Okay.
(Leonard:)Hey, I thought you were
trying to trick me.
(Penny:)Now, you just
get comfortable.
(Sheldon:)No, no, comfort is the enemy.
(Sheldon:)You know what's comfortable?
(Sheldon:)Slippers and blankets
and panda bears.
(Sheldon:)Imagine a panda bear with
Richard Feynman's face on it.
(Sheldon:)Warm up the car, Leonard,
it's poster time.
(Leonard:)Maybe in the morning.
(Penny:)Yeah, you get
some sleep.
(Sheldon:)No, I don't want to go
to sleep-- you can't make me.
(Penny:)You're right, we can't.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, darn straight, you can't.
(Sheldon:)Try to tell a grown man
to go to sleep...
♪ Soft kitty ♪
♪ Warm kitty ♪
♪ Little ball of fur... ♪
(Sheldon:)That's not gonna work.
♪ Happy kitty,
sleepy kitty ♪
♪ Purr ♪
BOTH:
♪ Purr, purr. ♪
(Leonard:)You know, he can be
a lot of trouble,
(Leonard:)but when I see him lying
here asleep like this,
(Leonard:)I just think...
(Leonard:)how easy it would be to
hold a pillow over his face.
Wow, you look like
you got some rest.
(Sheldon:)Oh, I'm feeling
much better.
(Sheldon:)And I've also been
continuing to make progress
(Sheldon:)without artificially
raising my anxiety levels.
(Leonard:)I turned on the heat in my car
and some vomit came out,
(Leonard:)so my levels--
right up there.
(Raj:)Hey, guys.
(Raj:)Mind if Emily
joins us for lunch?
(Leonard:)Yeah, sure.
Yeah, no problem.
Of course not.
(Emily:)So I hear you guys have been
playing a little game.
(Howard:)Well, um, we were
just kidding around.
(Emily:)Well, you may think it's funny
that Raj is sweet and sensitive,
(Emily:)but I think it's sexy.
(Emily:)Ugh, why is there dog hair
in your mouth?